{
    "subject": "resource/Guadalcanal_Diary_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Anthony_Quinn",
    "human_readable": "The film Guadalcanal Diary stars Anthony Quinn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9131105542182922,
            "question": "Who starred in the film Guadalcanal Diary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8508554697036743,
            "question": "Name an actor who was in the film Guadalcanal Diary."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7673805952072144,
            "question": "What kind of film is Guadalcanal Diary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7329666614532471,
            "question": "What other films has Anthony Quinn starred in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.717233419418335,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that Anthony Quinn appeared in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593109965324402,
            "question": "In which movie did Anthony Quinn have a leading role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4401914179325104,
            "question": "Is Anthony Quinn known for appearing in war films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43470272421836853,
            "question": "What historical event might the film Guadalcanal Diary be based on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.386310875415802,
            "question": "Are there any famous directors who worked on Guadalcanal Diary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28335264325141907,
            "question": "What genre does Guadalcanal Diary belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Guadalcanal Diary stars Anthony Quinn.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6683_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous directors who worked on Guadalcanal Diary?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6683_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical event might the film Guadalcanal Diary be based on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6683_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Anthony Quinn known for appearing in war films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6683_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6683_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Anthony Quinn is an actor who starred in the movie \"Guadalcanal Diary\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The film Guadalcanal Diary stars Anthony Quinn.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention Anthony Quinn as a star in the film, including:\n\n- Document `3.txt`: \"Guadalcanal Diary is a 1943 movie directed by Lewis Seiler starring Anthony Quinn and William Bendix.\"\n- Document `74.txt`: \"It was based on the book of the same name by Richard Tregaskis. Cast[] Preston Foster - Father Donnelly Lloyd Nolan - Sgt. Hook Malone William Bendix - Cpl. Anthony Quinn, Lloyd Nolan, on-set of the Film, 'Guadalcanal Diary', 1943\"\n- Document `96.txt`: \"starring Preston Foster, Lloyd Nolan, William Bendix, Richard Conte, Anthony Quinn and the film debut of Richard Jaeckel.\" \n\nThese references confirm that Anthony Quinn starred in the film Guadalcanal Diary."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}